[
  { "id": 1, "dan": 1, "question": "1 × 1", "answer": 1 },
  { "id": 2, "dan": 1, "question": "1 × 2", "answer": 2 },
  { "id": 3, "dan": 1, "question": "1 × 3", "answer": 3 },
  { "id": 4, "dan": 1, "question": "1 × 4", "answer": 4 },
  { "id": 5, "dan": 1, "question": "1 × 5", "answer": 5 },
  { "id": 6, "dan": 1, "question": "1 × 6", "answer": 6 },
  { "id": 7, "dan": 1, "question": "1 × 7", "answer": 7 },
  { "id": 8, "dan": 1, "question": "1 × 8", "answer": 8 },
  { "id": 9, "dan": 1, "question": "1 × 9", "answer": 9 },
  { "id": 10, "dan": 2, "question": "2 × 1", "answer": 2 },
  { "id": 11, "dan": 2, "question": "2 × 2", "answer": 4 },
  { "id": 12, "dan": 2, "question": "2 × 3", "answer": 6 },
  { "id": 13, "dan": 2, "question": "2 × 4", "answer": 8 },
  { "id": 14, "dan": 2, "question": "2 × 5", "answer": 10 },
  { "id": 15, "dan": 2, "question": "2 × 6", "answer": 12 },
  { "id": 16, "dan": 2, "question": "2 × 7", "answer": 14 },
  { "id": 17, "dan": 2, "question": "2 × 8", "answer": 16 },
  { "id": 18, "dan": 2, "question": "2 × 9", "answer": 18 },
  { "id": 19, "dan": 3, "question": "3 × 1", "answer": 3 },
  { "id": 20, "dan": 3, "question": "3 × 2", "answer": 6 },
  { "id": 21, "dan": 3, "question": "3 × 3", "answer": 9 },
  { "id": 22, "dan": 3, "question": "3 × 4", "answer": 12 },
  { "id": 23, "dan": 3, "question": "3 × 5", "answer": 15 },
  { "id": 24, "dan": 3, "question": "3 × 6", "answer": 18 },
  { "id": 25, "dan": 3, "question": "3 × 7", "answer": 21 },
  { "id": 26, "dan": 3, "question": "3 × 8", "answer": 24 },
  { "id": 27, "dan": 3, "question": "3 × 9", "answer": 27 },
  { "id": 28, "dan": 4, "question": "4 × 1", "answer": 4 },
  { "id": 29, "dan": 4, "question": "4 × 2", "answer": 8 },
  { "id": 30, "dan": 4, "question": "4 × 3", "answer": 12 },
  { "id": 31, "dan": 4, "question": "4 × 4", "answer": 16 },
  { "id": 32, "dan": 4, "question": "4 × 5", "answer": 20 },
  { "id": 33, "dan": 4, "question": "4 × 6", "answer": 24 },
  { "id": 34, "dan": 4, "question": "4 × 7", "answer": 28 },
  { "id": 35, "dan": 4, "question": "4 × 8", "answer": 32 },
  { "id": 36, "dan": 4, "question": "4 × 9", "answer": 36 },
  { "id": 37, "dan": 5, "question": "5 × 1", "answer": 5 },
  { "id": 38, "dan": 5, "question": "5 × 2", "answer": 10 },
  { "id": 39, "dan": 5, "question": "5 × 3", "answer": 15 },
  { "id": 40, "dan": 5, "question": "5 × 4", "answer": 20 },
  { "id": 41, "dan": 5, "question": "5 × 5", "answer": 25 },
  { "id": 42, "dan": 5, "question": "5 × 6", "answer": 30 },
  { "id": 43, "dan": 5, "question": "5 × 7", "answer": 35 },
  { "id": 44, "dan": 5, "question": "5 × 8", "answer": 40 },
  { "id": 45, "dan": 5, "question": "5 × 9", "answer": 45 },
  { "id": 46, "dan": 6, "question": "6 × 1", "answer": 6 },
  { "id": 47, "dan": 6, "question": "6 × 2", "answer": 12 },
  { "id": 48, "dan": 6, "question": "6 × 3", "answer": 18 },
  { "id": 49, "dan": 6, "question": "6 × 4", "answer": 24 },
  { "id": 50, "dan": 6, "question": "6 × 5", "answer": 30 },
  { "id": 51, "dan": 6, "question": "6 × 6", "answer": 36 },
  { "id": 52, "dan": 6, "question": "6 × 7", "answer": 42 },
  { "id": 53, "dan": 6, "question": "6 × 8", "answer": 48 },
  { "id": 54, "dan": 6, "question": "6 × 9", "answer": 54 },
  { "id": 55, "dan": 7, "question": "7 × 1", "answer": 7 },
  { "id": 56, "dan": 7, "question": "7 × 2", "answer": 14 },
  { "id": 57, "dan": 7, "question": "7 × 3", "answer": 21 },
  { "id": 58, "dan": 7, "question": "7 × 4", "answer": 28 },
  { "id": 59, "dan": 7, "question": "7 × 5", "answer": 35 },
  { "id": 60, "dan": 7, "question": "7 × 6", "answer": 42 },
  { "id": 61, "dan": 7, "question": "7 × 7", "answer": 49 },
  { "id": 62, "dan": 7, "question": "7 × 8", "answer": 56 },
  { "id": 63, "dan": 7, "question": "7 × 9", "answer": 63 },
  { "id": 64, "dan": 8, "question": "8 × 1", "answer": 8 },
  { "id": 65, "dan": 8, "question": "8 × 2", "answer": 16 },
  { "id": 66, "dan": 8, "question": "8 × 3", "answer": 24 },
  { "id": 67, "dan": 8, "question": "8 × 4", "answer": 32 },
  { "id": 68, "dan": 8, "question": "8 × 5", "answer": 40 },
  { "id": 69, "dan": 8, "question": "8 × 6", "answer": 48 },
  { "id": 70, "dan": 8, "question": "8 × 7", "answer": 56 },
  { "id": 71, "dan": 8, "question": "8 × 8", "answer": 64 },
  { "id": 72, "dan": 8, "question": "8 × 9", "answer": 72 },
  { "id": 73, "dan": 9, "question": "9 × 1", "answer": 9 },
  { "id": 74, "dan": 9, "question": "9 × 2", "answer": 18 },
  { "id": 75, "dan": 9, "question": "9 × 3", "answer": 27 },
  { "id": 76, "dan": 9, "question": "9 × 4", "answer": 36 },
  { "id": 77, "dan": 9, "question": "9 × 5", "answer": 45 },
  { "id": 78, "dan": 9, "question": "9 × 6", "answer": 54 },
  { "id": 79, "dan": 9, "question": "9 × 7", "answer": 63 },
  { "id": 80, "dan": 9, "question": "9 × 8", "answer": 72 },
  { "id": 81, "dan": 9, "question": "9 × 9", "answer": 81 }
]
